天啊...
God...
这里是911 请问你发生紧急情况的
911 , what's the address
地址是哪里
to your emergency?
我想报告在我的公寓楼里
i-i'd like to report a domestic dispute
发生的一起家庭纠纷
in my apartment building .
你发生紧急情况的地址是哪里
And what is the address to your emergency ?
等等
Hold on .
格林布什大道4200号 四号公寓
It's 4200 Greenbush Avenue, a-apartment four .
我不能...
Can't...
不 不 我不能
No,no,i can't .
不行 我不能一直打电话
No,i can't stay on the phone .
他在打她
He's hitting her .
女士们 先生们 打起精神来
Ladies and gents , brace yourselves .
我有个坏消息
i have some bad news .
美国影视男演员
扎克·埃夫隆退圈了
Zac Efron is off the market .
接下来的一段并非漏译 官方也无字幕
验收测试
诚邀您3月4日下午1点10分
于皇家酒店302房间
参加匿名无条件与仰慕者
进行性关系的活动
请勾选您的性趣爱好
有什么好消息吗
Anything good ?
是个婚礼请柬
It's a wedding invitation .
比我们的还要好吗
Nicer than ours ?
不可能
Not a Chance .
好吧
All right .
我想我们周日可以去宴席承办商那里
I was thinking we could go to the caterer's on Sunday ,
试试新的菜单
try out that new menu .
哦 是的 我很喜欢听起来不错
oh , yeah , I love it , that sounds great .
你知道 如果我们今晚不想
You know , if we don't end up feeling like seeing
见到PJ和劳伦 我们可以取消
PJ and Lauren tonight , we can cancel ,
完全没关系的
it's totally fine .
哦 好的 可以
oh , okay , yeah , yeah , yeah , yeah .
好吧 我该告诉他吗
All right , should i tell him ?
- 是的 - 好吧 这是...
- Yes. - All right fine , it's...
好吧 那么几个月来
All right . So for months ,
我们试图联系那家伙的团队
we were trying to get in touch with the guy's team ,
我们想把这家伙签到经纪公司
we're trying to sign the guy to the agency .
一直没有回复 我们竭尽所能
No answer . We're doing everything we can
试图联系他的上司 所有能联系的人
trying to reach the guy's higher ups , everything .
我们试了所有可能的电子邮件地址组合
We're trying every possible combination of email address ,
一点用也没有
doesn't work , nothing , all right ?
我读了很多关于美第奇家族的书
So I've been reading a lot about the Medici family .
这些家伙 他们拥有世界上所有的钱
These guys , they got all the money in the world ,
他们与世隔绝
they're secluded from everVbody .
所以我在想
And I was thinking , and I was like ,
这些有钱人
these rich people ,
他们根本没有社交媒体
they don't have social media .
你不能和这些人联系
You can't get in touch with these people .
他们没有Facebook之类的东西
They don't have Facebook or anything .
但是你可以假设这些混蛋肯定有Venmo
But you can bet these motherfuckers have Venmo .
不可能
No
哦 是的 兄弟
oh , yeah , bro .
所以我给那家伙发Venmo请求 花了两便士
So I send the guy a Venmo request for two pennies
希望他能让我和乔丹做他的经纪人
to get his two cents about Jordan and I being his agents .
有用吗
And that worked ?
当然有用 所以我才点了香槟
Fuck yeah , it worked . That's why I ordered champagne .
我们明天要和他的团队见面
We're meeting with his team tomorrow .
美丽的新世界
Brave new world .
这合法吗
Is that legal ?
怎么 我们会有麻烦吗
What , are we gonna get in trouble ?
不好意思
Excuse me ,
你能给我们结下帐吗
could we get a check when you get a chance ?
4月11日就快到了
April 11th is coming up soon .
你们婚礼计划得怎么样
Are you all deep into wedding plans ?
是啊 还有不到两个月的时间
Yeah , less than two months .
要做的事情很多
Yeah，there's a lot .
我们的家人
Our families
我是我姐妹中最后一个结婚的
I'm the last of my sisters to get married
所以压力很大
So there's a lot of stress
座位安排之类的
around where people are going to sit .
但你会想起 这是一个开放的酒吧
But then you remember it's an open bar
几乎可以自己运转
and will practically run itself .
如果一切都搞砸了 我们就离开
And if it does all fall apart , we're skipping town .
我们去度蜜月
We're doing a road trip honeymoon .
这是我的主意
It was my idea .
哦 我那个和我们一起住的朋友
oh , that friend of mine that was staying with us...
- 我们可以告诉他们吗 - 可以 你可以告诉他们
- Are we allowed to tell them？- Yeah , you can tell'em .
我一个伯克利的朋友
okay , so a friend of mine from Berkeley ,
她和我们住在一起 她是个空中乘务员
she was staying with us , right ? She's a flight attendant .
她给我们讲了很多关于飞机上的疯狂故事
She was telling us all these crazy stories about flying .
像是他们打算把飞机翻个底朝天
Like they have plans to flip the plane upside down
就只为了以防有恐怖分子 有时还不得不提前降落
in case there's a terrorist , and having to land early
因为有些人有焦虑症
because of people having anxiety attacks ,
非常有趣 非常疯狂
really interesting stuff , really insane .
不管怎样 她给我们讲了一个故事
Anyway , she was telling us a story about
一次完全正常的飞行中
a totally normal flight ,
这个女人和她丈夫在头等舱
and this woman and her husband are in first class
应该是去度蜜月 我猜啊
for their honeymoon , I guess ,
他们要下飞机了
and they're getting off the plane
然后那个女人倒下了
and the woman collapses ,
年轻的女人 新婚夫妇
young woman , newlyweds .
显然她很漂亮 对吧
And she is beautiful apparently , right ?
他们发现她身上有血迹
They realize she's got blood on her ,
但她说她没事
but she says she's fine ,
没人知道发生了什么
nobody knows what's going on .
美国运输安全管理局介入了
The TSA gets involved .
他们意识到她身上的一些血迹已经干了
They realize that some of the blood has dried on her .
发现她和她丈夫
Turns out , she and her husband
他们吵了一架 天知道是为了什么
got into a fight about God knows what
然后用飞机上的香槟酒瓶
and he stabbed her in the ribs
刺穿了她的肋骨
with an in-flight champagne bottle .
所以他们都认为这是性交易 但事实并非如此
So they all think it's a sex trafficking thing but it's not .
他们把所有人都带走了 她告诉运输安全管理局
They bring everybody in . She tells the TSA
他们都从事着形象至上的工作
they both work in careers where image is everything
她只是不想让别人知道
and she just didn't want anybody to know
他们一直在吵架
that they'd been fighting .
这是不是很疯狂
Isn't that insane ?
非常感谢你们的光临
Thank you guys so much for coming in .
- 谢谢 - 非常感谢
- Thank you - Thank you so much .
- 谢谢 - 谢谢
- Thank you - Thank you .
哦 你可以吗
oh , could you ?
我的意思是我只喝了一杯酒
I mean I only had one glass of wine .
是吗 因为我觉得你喝了三四杯
Did you？ 'Cause I feel like you had about three or four .
通常那时你会开始讲你的长篇大论
That's when you usually start telling your long stories .
我肯定没吃羊肉串 这太疯狂了
I definitely didn't have the lamb kebabs , that's crazy .
我讨厌羊肉 从来不点那个
I hate lamb , would never order that .
不 不
No , no
是的
Yes .
APE 我是艾米
APE , this is Amy .
那么什么是包装交易呢
So what is a packaging deal ?
包装交易是当一个电视节目或电影
Packaging deals are large payments
因我们在这个项目背后安排的创意团队而获得绿灯时
that we get when a TV show or movie is greenlit
我们获得的大笔报酬
for us having arranged the creative team behind a project .
这是一份附属的合同 通常是私人合同
It is an ancillary , often private contract ,
让我们能够行使我们的权力
that allows us to wield our power
以远高于我们
to enter deals for wav more than the 10%
从客户群中赚取的10％的价格达成交易
we're making from our client pool .
这里面不存在所谓的问题
There's no such thing as problems , okay ?
只有机会
only opportunities .
现在WGA的那些混蛋们
Now , the cocksuckers at the WGA
试图告诉所有人包装的事
trying to tell everybody about packaging
让他们的成员离开我们的代理机构
and getting their members to leave our agency
这是我们有史以来面临的最大机会
is the biggest opportunity we've ever faced .
这将意味着我们增长的终结
It would mean the end of growth for us .
这意味着这栋建筑
Now , what that means is that this building here ,
我们现在所处的这个结构...
this structure that we're in right now , um...
它不会...
it won't...
它不再存在
It won't be around anymore .
- 嗨 乔丹 - 嗯
- Hi , Jordan - Yes .
我安装了那个
I installed that Chrome extengion
可以祝你的朋友生日快乐的Chrome扩展程序...
that wishes your friends happy birthday...
- 嗯 - PJ在找你
- Uh-huh -And PJ's looking for you .
中国的人提前30分钟来了
The China team arrived 30 minutes early .
嗯 好的 等等 对不起 你说中国的来了
Uh-huh , okay , wait , sorry , you said China's here ?
中国的人现在就在这里吗
China's here right now ?
- 为什么中国的人在这里 - 乔丹 乔丹
一Why is China here？- Jordan , Jordan .
嘿 嘿 雷蒙德来了 中国来了 快点
Hey , hey , Raymond's here . China's here . Come on .
杰克琳 我是被从电子邮件链上除名了吗
Jaclyn , was I taken off of the email chain ?
我们应该在大厅见面
We're supposed to meet in the lobby
闲聊和握手
for Small talk and handshakes .
这是心理学基础
That's Psychology 10I .
你让我把你从电子邮件链上撤下来的
You asked me to take you off that email chain .
- 嘿 PJ - 好吧 把我放回去
- Hey , PJ - okay , well put me back on
嘿 是啊 随便了 他们正在谈论新的制作
Hey , yeah , whatever . They're talking new productions .
他们喜欢漫威 他们想要我们的名单
They love Marvel . They want our roster .
- 知道了吗 太好了 - 我喜欢很刺激
- okay ? Great - I love it , it's exciting .
事情在发展很令人兴奋 我可以带你到嗨上天
Things are moving , it's exciting . I can take you to 100%.
拍马屁对这家伙没用好吗
Flattery's not gonna work on this guy , okay ?
他很聪明 伙计 我们做到了
He's smart . Dude , we did this .
他妻子的名字叫劳拉 他支持中国政府
His wife's name's Laura . He supports the Chinese government .
这是我们和CAA之间的事 我不会让这种事再次发生
It's between us and CAA . I will not let this happen again .
去他妈的CAA 那应该是我的品牌 来吧
Fuck CAA , that should be my license plate . Come on .
不 还给我
Nope , actually , give me that back .
嘿 伙计 忘了你的婚礼请柬吧
Hey , dude , forget about your wedding invitation
就他妈的五秒钟 好吗
for five fucking seconds , okay ?
你不让他坐下 你说 我们继续谈吧
You don't let him sit . You say ,"Let's keep talking .
我们继续聊吧 用中文说欢迎意味着
Let's keep talking ."Hunying means
欢迎加入我们的队伍 你必须把它说对了
welcome to the team and you've got to get it right .
乔丹 这是可是中国啊
Jordan , this is China .
欢迎
Hunying .
好的 很好来吧
okay great . Come on .
- 他来了 - 嘿 我的好兄弟
- Hey , there he is - Hey , there's my guy .
- 乔丹·海因斯 你好吗 - 你好
- Jordan Hines , how are you？- Ni hao .
你好 你好 你怎么样
Ni hao ,"ni how" the hell are ya ?
欢迎来到好莱坞
Welcome to Hollywood .
- 要咖啡吗 - 不 我不要咖啡
- Want some coffee？ - No , no coffee for me ,
谢谢 我有溃疡
thank you , I have an ulcer .
我们那个笨蛋助手
Our bonehead of an asgigtant
- 肯定是误传了... - 溃疡是什么
- must've miscommunicated... - What's an ulcer ?
溃疡 没什么
An ulcer , oh , uh , it's nothing .
这个...这个...
It's , uh...It's uh...
是我内脏上的一个开放性的疮
It's an open sore on my insides .
它可能会杀了我
It might kill me .
旅途偷快吗
How was your flight ?
没事的 没事的
Uh , it's fine . No , no , it's fine .
这是... 是个假警报 没事的
It's , uh...No , it's false alarm , it's okay .
请坐 请坐...不 请坐
Please have a seat . Please , have a...No，have a seat .
请坐 请坐
Please , no , please , have a seat .
是的 请坐 大家请坐
Yeah , have a seat , everybody have a seat .
这很令人兴奋 我很兴奋
It's exciting . I'm excited .
我很兴奋
I am excited .
这很令人兴奋
It's exciting .
一切正常
Everything's fine .
拿下交易
Just get the package .
只要拿下包装交易就行
Just get the packaging deal .
这座建筑没有倒塌
The building isn't collapsing .
我们继续聊吧 我很兴奋
Well let's keep talking . I'm excited .
那我们继续聊吧
Well , let's keep talking .
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey !
女士 不要朝我的车扔东西
Ma'am! Don't throw shit at my car .
这车是我租来的
I lease this fucking car .
女士
Ma'am!
搞什么
What the fuck ?
是他吗
Is that him ?
是的 就是他
Yeah , that's him .
对不起 我们不需要待很久
Sorry , we don't have to stay long .
当你想签下这样的人
It's important to come across as enthusiastic and authentic
表现出热情和真实是很重要的
when you're signing someone like this ,
因为这是一个非常重大的承诺
when it's this big of a commitment .
我很快就送你回家
I'm gonna get you home soon .
- 去吧 - 好的
-Go for it - okay .
雷蒙德 我是乔丹·海恩斯 你好吗
Raymond , Jordan Hines , how are you ?
抓到了
Got you .
- 我很喜欢 - 当然
-I love it - Of course you do .
我想把你介绍给我未来的妻子卡罗琳
I wanted to introduce you to my future wife , Caroline ,
应该他妈的就在这里某个地方...
who's fucking here somewhere . Um...
随便了 给自己拿杯喝的 好吗
Whatever , grab yourself a drink , huh ?
不了 我今晚还要开车 我已经戒酒五年了
No , I'm just the driver tonight , five years sober .
我想确认一下
I wanted to , um , make sure
在你回中国之前
that you had everything that you needed
你得到了你需要的一切
before you left to go to China
我们的机构代理了很多知识产权
and our agency represents a lot of intellectual property .
所以如果你想把任何东西
So if there's ever anything that you wanted
制作成电视节目或电影
To make into a TV Show or a movie
即使是你读过的一篇文章
even if there's an article that you read maybe
我们也很乐意去获得这些版权
we'd be happy to look into acquiring those rights-
- 所有人 - 好吧
-Everyone! - Yeah .
对不起 各位
Excuse me , everyone .
无声拍卖25分钟后结束
The silent auction ends in 25 minutes
现在开始出价吧
So place your bids .
所有东西都是免税的
Everything is tax deductible ,
而且这是为了一个伟大的事业
and it's for a great cause .
所以别小气好吗
So don't be cheap , huh ?
说到小气
And speaking of cheap ,
我正看着那些偷偷摸摸进来的混蛋经纪人
I'm looking at these piece of shit agents who snuck in .
是的 是的
Yeah , yeah .
- 他真是个人物 - 你知道会发生什么
一He's a character - You know what happens
如果你小气的话 会发生什么
if you cheap , what happens ?
是的
Yeah .
非常感谢你过来
Thank you so much for stopping by .
非常感谢您邀请我们
Thank you so much for having us .
我想问你在哪里订的花
wanted to ask where did you order the flowers ?
我从一个网站上订的
I got them from a website .
- 法国百合吗 - 没错
一Fleur-de-Lis？ - That's right .
嗯 我们婚礼也用这个
Yeah , that's who we're using for the wedding .
- 亲爱的 它们真漂亮 - 是啊 它们真漂亮
- Honey , aren't they beautiful. - Yeah , they're gorgeous .
我们生活在未来是不是很兴奋
We live in the future , isn't that exciting ?
你什么时候结婚
When are you getting married ?
非常非常快了
Very , very soon .
亲爱的
Honey ?
- 你没事吧 - 没事 一切都好
-Are you all right？ -Yeah , everything's fine .
我要...我要跟他说点什么
I'm just gonna...I'm gonna say something to him .
我就要失去他了 我只想...
I'm gonna lose him and I just wanna...
让我再试一次
Let me just...Give me one more try ,
再给我一次机会
Just give me one more try .
雷蒙德 我只是想说
Raymond , uh , I just wanted to say
非常感谢邀请我们
thank you so much for having us .
我和未婚妻要走了
My fiance and I are leaving ,
我想对你说最后一件事
and I wanted to say one last thing to you ,
我们不是《明星伙伴》中
that we're not the angry bulldogs
所说的愤怒的斗牛犬
that Entourage makes us out to be .
我认为电视剧倾向于把我们塑造成
I think television tends to make us out to be
这些愤怒的小人物
these angry petty people .
电影业的很多方面也随着哈维的倒台名声臭了些
But a lot of that film industry aspect left with Harvey .
这他妈的是谁
Who the fuck is this ?
但世界正在进入一个非常令人兴奋的时代
So the world is entering into this really exciting time
一个数字国际增长时代我们也是其中的一部分
of digital international growth and we're a part of it .
而我们团队的工作方式
And the way that our team works ,
我觉得我们包装项目的方式
I feel like it could make life very exciting for you
会让你的生活变得非常令人兴奋
with the way that we package our projects .
我不需要任何包装
I don't need anything packaged .
你编这个词只是为了偷别人钱
That's a term you made up to steal people's money ,
你周围的一切都将崩溃
and it's all gonna collapse around you .
我们不需要经纪人帮忙来预订我们的旅行
We don't need agents to book our travel .
我们不需要经纪人假装自己是制片人
We don't need agents to pretend to be producers .
你是一个濒临灭绝的社会网络
You are a dying social network ,
每个人都迫不及待地想看你崩溃
and everyone can't wait to watch you fall apart .
我们继续聊吧
Well let's keep talking .
喜欢这种坦诚
Love the honesty .
我们喜欢这样
We love that．
谢谢邀请我们
Thank you for having us .
你的溃疡怎么样了
How is your ulcer ?
没什么事 有点要命而已
It's fine . Killing me .
所以 是的 他是一个很有趣的人物
So , yeah , he's a really interesting character .
我和他进行了一次很好的长谈
I had a good long conversation with him .
不是不行 他会考虑的
It's not a no , he's gonna think about it .
我们要保持谈话的开放性
We're gonna keep the conversation open .
PJ说他会在早上给他打电话
PJ said he would call him in the morning .
他很接近了 他会搞定的
He's the closer , he'll close the deal .
我们离开前他确实抓住了我的腹股沟
He did grab me in the groin before we left .
我想这是一种文化差异吧
I think it's a cultural thing .
如果他和CAA签约 这并不是世界上最糟糕的事情
And if he signs with CAA , it's not the worst thing in the world .
他仍然可以成为一个备选客户
He could still be a hip pocket client .
我们仍然可以为他包装一些东西
We could still package some things for him .
也许现在就可以把他的一些中国知识产权带到美国
Maybe bring some of his Chinese intellectual property
然后通过我们的进行开发
to the United states and develop it under our studio wing now .
是的 我们今天早上刚签下泰格·伍兹当导演
And , yeah , we just signed Tiger Woods as a director this morning .
他们要重拍《疯狂高尔夫》
They're gonna reboot Caddyshack with dogs .
所以今晚的一切
So all in all tonight , yeah ,
今晚对每个人来说都是美好的一晚
tonight was a great night for everybody .
酷
Cool.
亲爱的 出什么事了吗
Honey , is anything going on ?
我吗
With me ?
没有亲爱的 怎么了
No , honey . What ?
我们大概六周后就要结婚了
We're getting married in , like , six weeks .
如果发生了什么事 我会告诉你的
If anything were going on , I'd let you know .
他妈想别想
No fucking way .
有人吗
Hello ?
嘿 我的好兄弟
Hey , there's my guy .
你想做些有用的事情吗
Do you want to do something helpful ?
我的好兄弟
There's my guy . There he is
你真勇敢
Oh, you're so brave .
是令人兴奋的 令人兴奋 我们很兴奋 我们很喜欢
这
It's exciting . Exciting . We're excited . We love it .
我们很兴奋 我们很兴奋
We're excited . We're excited .
我们都很兴奋 继续聊吧
We're all excited . Let's keep talking .
我们继续聊 继续聊
Let's keep talking . Let's keep talking .
特伦斯 我刚收到你加入WGA的邮件
Terrence , I just got the email about you Joining the WGA .
很遗憾听到这个消息
I'm so sorry to hear that .
我正准备把你推荐给
I was just about to put you forward
一个电视节目的编剧室
for a television show in the writer's room .
但是发生了什么呢
But what happened ?
我以为你想出名
I thought you wanted to be famous .
好吧 假设说一些演员来找你
okay , so let's say some actor comes up to you
说你没给他们找到工作
and says you can't get them work .
你说 去拍张新的简历照
You say ,"Get new headshots .
你打的是我家的电话
You're calling on my family phone ."
这就是令人兴奋的地方
Well , that's what's so exciting is the audience for television
电视的观众比独立电影的观众多得多
is so much larger than independent film .
你还想继续制作这些
How much longer do you want to keep making stuff
没人看到东西多久
that nobody's seeing ?
转移 攻击 用犯罪者取代受害者
Deflect , attack , replace victim with offender ,
D . A . R . V . O .
D . A . R . V . O
想象一下你的孩子们正在挨饿
Picture that your children , starving ,
而这些WGA成员
and these WGA members just standing
不要流媒体
有线电视＝$
就站在你的孩子上方笑着...
above your children and laughing...
因为他们就是这么做的
'cause that's what they're doing .
这就是所有WGA成员正在做的
That's what all of the WGA is doing .
他们在嘲笑你饥饿的孩子
They're laughing at your starving children .
他妈的放松五秒钟 我在打电话
Relax for five fucking seconds . I'm on the phone .
太恶心了
It's Sick .
我们过于强大 不容失败
We're too strong to fail .
We are too strong to fail .
我们过于强大 不容失败 我们过于强大 不容失败
We're too strong to fail . We are too strong to fail .
去你的
是啊 我有辆特斯拉 我们都很兴奋
Yeah .I own a Tesla . We're excited .
你是全身心属于我的吗
Are you all mine ?
是的
I am .
包装经纪公司
最近删除
彻底删除2张照片
嘿
Hey.
可以给我一个吗
May I have one ?
当然
oh , sure.
你在这里会做的很好
You'll do great here .
杰克琳 进来坐吧
Jaclyn , come on in , have a seat .
好吧
oh , okay .
近来可好
How are you ?
你的人生目标是什么
What do you want to do with your life ?
我还不知道
Uh...well , I don't know yet .
- 呃 这个吧 - 是啊 没错
- Uh , this - Yeah , right .
没有人想永远呆在这里
Nobody wants to be here forever .
每个人都想要别的东西
Everybody wants something else .
你想要什么
What do you want ?
- 说实话 这就是我的理想 - 说实话 这就是你的理想
- Honestly , I do - Honestly , you do .
你是从梅伯里来的吗
What are you from Mayberry ?
你是从《安迪·格里菲斯秀》来的吗
What are you from the Andy Griffith Show ?
谁会这么说话
Who talks like that？
我能为你做什么 我能帮上什么忙
What can I do for you ? How can I help ?
我们总是把托尼·罗宾斯推出去
We have all these retreats where we wheel out Tony Robbins
让他告诉我们 我们有多幸福
and he tells us how happy we are
如何掌控公司 如何控制局面
how to take over the town , take control.
你为什么不停止每天
Why don't you stop lying to everybody in the office
对办公室里的每个人撒谎
all day every day
最终承认你真正想要的是什么
and finally admit what you actually want ?
杰克琳想要什么
What does Jaclyn want ?
好吧
Okay.
你能帮我联系一下
Could you put me in touch with the investment firm
我听到你和雷蒙德的团队谈论的投资公司吗
I heard you and Raymond's team talking about ?
好的 我会的
Yes , I will
华尔街是吗
Wall Street ?
看这不是很简单吗
See , wasn't that easy ?
现在你不会让它从内心吞噬你了
Now you're not letting that eat at you from the inside .
感觉不错吧
Doesn't that feel good ?
是的 你心情不错
It does . You're in a good mood .
你妻子今天早上坐在你脸上了吗
Did your wife sit on your face this morning ?
你说什么
What'd you say ?
你今天早上醒来时是不是睡在床的右边了吗
Did you wake up on the right side of the bed this morning ?
这是一种说法
It's an expression .
哦 是的 我想...我想是的
oh . Yeah , I guess I...I guess I did .
太好了 谢谢
Well , great . Thanks for this .
我得改一下我的简历 把为你工作写在上面
I'll have to change my resume to list working for you on it .
你能给我留出明天的时间吗
Could you give me till tomorrow ?
当然...没什么
Yeah , of course...Yeah , it's nothing .
哦 还有会计方面的问题
oh , and accounting had questions
公司信用卡上有一万美元的支出...
about a $10,000 charge that was put on the company card...
没事的 我会处理
Yeah , that's fine , I'll take care of that ,
- 谢谢 - 门开着还是关着
- Thank you - open or closed ?
关上吧 谢谢
Close that door , thank you .
啊 不对 她说了
Ah！No，she said it .
嘿 你来得真早
Hey , you're here early .
我才刚刚打开咖啡机
We just started the Keurig .
杰克琳
Hey Jaclyn ,
我能和你谈谈吗
can I talk to you for a second ?
当然 怎么了
Yeah , sure , what's up ?
昨天我们在我的办公室
So we were in my office yesterday
我好像听到你说什么了
and I thought I heard you say something
我只是想确认你说过
and I just want to make sure that you had said it .
没什么大不了的 你又没惹什么麻烦
It's not a big deal . You're not in trouble or anything .
- 嘿 麦琪 - 嗨 乔丹
- Hey , Maggie - Hi , Jordan .
但我说我会介绍你和贝莱德的人联系
But I said that I would connect you with the people at Black Rock
然后你说了一些关于
and then you said something about waking up on
在床的右边醒来的事情
the right side of the bed .
你还记得你到底说了什么吗
Do you remember what you actually said ?
我不太明白
I'm not sure I understand .
- 好吧 - 如果真的造成困扰的话
- okay - If it's a big deal ,
其实也没那么重要
it's really not that important .
我已经让我的男朋友帮我写简历了
I had my boyfriend work on my resume with me .
如果我说了不该说的话 我很抱歉
I'm sorry if I said something I shouldn't have .
- 嗯 - 我越界了吗
- Uh-huh - Was I out of line ?
- 我很抱歉 如果我有的话 - 我相信你没有
I'm so sorry if I was - I'm sure you weren't
你没说其他的吗
And you didn't say anything ?
天啊 你以为我说了什么
oh , my God . What do you think I said ?
好吧 这很好 所以这是一次失败好吗
Okay , so this is great . So this is a failure , okay ?
所以我现在不能用我想对你们说的语言
So I can't use the language that I'd like to use to you right now
因为该机构
because of the new direction
和国家正朝着新的方向发展 所以我不会
that the agency and the country is going so I won't ,
我只能说这不管用
andI'll Just say that this isn't working .
好吗 这一切都不是 你不是在为我工作
okay ? All this isn't , you aren't working for me .
那么你明天来的时候是什么样子
So how are you gonna come in tomorrow ?
今天就到此为止好吗
Let's call today a wash , okay ?
你明天来的时候是什么样子呢
How are you gonna come in tomorrow ?
因为有一排刚毕业的大学生
'Cause there is a line of recent college graduates
迫不及待地想来这里工作
that are just dying to come in here and work ,
坐在那个该死的座位上
to sit in that fucking seat .
告诉我 你明天来的时候会是什么样子
So tell me , how are you gonna look tomorrow when you come in ?
你今天要怎么说服我
How are you gonna convince me today
你明天的工作会做得更好
that you're better at your fucking Job tomorrow ,
杰奎琳
Jacqueline ?
我会做得更好
I'll do better .
我还是新来的
I'm still new here .
很高兴听到这个消息 把简历发过来
That's great to hear . Send over that resume .
我迫不及待地想把它发给新朋友了
I cannot wait to send it out to new people .
代我向你男朋友问好
Tell your boyfriend I said thanks
别再用我的电脑了
and don't go on my computer again .
关于我的私生活
You don't know the first fucking thing
你他妈什么都不知道
about my personal life .
还有在午饭后
And I am gonna need new Pepto-Bismol
我需要新的胃药
immediately after lunch .
这就是好莱坞
Hollywood .
操
Fuck .
操 嘿
Fuck . Hey !
你好有什么可以帮你的吗
Hello , how can I help you ?
你好吗 我想知道我是否能得到
How are you ? I'm wondering if I can get
一张打印出来的住宿收据
a receipt printed out for my stay .
几周前我住在这里
I stayed here a few weeks ago
我的助手在清理我的车
and my assistant was cleaning out a car that I own
一定是像个白痴一样把它扔了
and must've thrown it away like a fucking idiot .
哦 这种事时有发生 你有身份证明的复印件吗
oh , well that happens . Do you have a copy of your ID ?
我有 但并不是我订的房间
I do , but I didn't make the reservation .
我在一家大公司工作我不知道
I work for a big company and I'm not sure who's name
- 用谁的名字订的 - 我明白了
- it would have been under - I See .
这么说你不知道订房间人的名字是吗
So you don't know the name the reservation was made under ?
我不知道 但应该是3月4日
I don't , but it would've been the 4th of March
下午1点10分左右 在320房间
in room 320 at about l:10 p.m.
我也不确定 可能是任何时候
or I'm uncertain , it could have been anytime .
好吧
Okay .
不幸的是 它不让我搜索这个
Well , unfortunately it won't let me search for that .
有没有什么办法可以知道预订人名字或卡号
is there a way you can get the name or card number
预订人名字吗
of the person who made the reservation ?
好吧 我已经说过了
Okay , so I already said that there isn't .
我在一家大型人才经纪公司工作
I work for a big talent agency
我可不是小人物 是大人物
and I'm not a small fry over there , the big one .
就几个字母 我让你猜三次
A couple letters , I'll give you three guesses .
你只需要猜中一次 我就要结婚了
You're only gonna need one . I'm getting married soon ,
我不知道是谁造成了...
and I don't know who would have made the reser...
你从事电影行业吗
Are you in the film industry ?
我不从事
I'm not .
现在如果你可以打电话给别人
Now if you can call someone ,
我们可以马上给你
we can get that to you immediately ,
但这是酒店的隐私政策 我很抱歉
but it's hotel privacy policy , I'm so sorry .
- 如果我被抢劫了怎么办 - 抱歉 如果什么
- What if I was robbed？- I'm sorry , if what ?
假设我只在房间里待了17分钟
Let's say I was only in the room for 17 minutes
有人从我的保险箱里偷了东西
and somebody stole something from my safe ,
如果我还认为你们两个以及酒店
and what if I also thought that you two at the hotel
和这件事有关呢
had something to do with it ?
实际上我不知道这种事的规章制度
I actually don't know the protocol for something like that .
但我觉得我们会报警
I think we'd have to call the police .
如果我是警察呢
And what if I am the police ?
先生 如果你是警察
Sir , if you were the police ,
你可能会提前打电话
you would've probably called ahead of time
而且在我询要的时候你也会给我看你的身份证明
and you also would've shown me your ID when I asked for it
这样你就不会花45分钟
and maybe you wouldn't have spent 45 minutes
告诉我你是个多么出色的好莱坞经纪人
telling me how big of a Hollywood agent you are .
是的 的确...是的
Yeah , that's...Yeah .
今天还有什么需要我们帮忙的吗
Is there anything else we can help you with today ?
没了 我想没有了
No , I don't think that there is
- 谢谢你的光临 - 谢谢招待
- Well , thanks for coming in - Thanks for having me .
我的肚子咕咕叫着说
I've got this rumbling stomach that says ,
是的 我需要食物
yeah , I need food .
-我饿坏了..．- 抱歉 继续
-I'm ravenous and I... - Hey , so sorry , keep going .
我也需要那些贪婪的人
And I need people that are ravenous too .
我需要饥饿的人们
I need people that are hungry .
我去吃意式料理的时候
When I go to Buca di Beppo ,
我要了一个超级大份意大利宽面 那个服务员
I order a Fettuccine Supreme and that server ,
她拿出来说...
she brings out and says...
- 这个会议是关于什么的 - WGA包装
- What is this meeting about？ - WGA packaging .
- 什么 - WGA包装
- What is it？ - WGA packaging .
不行 我们可不做这个
Nope , uh-uh , no , we're not doing that .
抱歉 继续说 我今天没时间
Uh , sorry , keep going . I just don't have time for it today .
我不知道会是这样
I didn't know that that was gonna be what this was about .
我最初想来这里谈的是...
What I initially wanted to come in here to talkto about...
没关系 没关系 我们过于强大 不容失败
It's fine . It's fine , we're too strong to fail ,
大家都做得很好
everybody's doing great .
我想和PJ谈谈 看看你有没有那东西
I wanted to talk to PJ and see if you have that thing .
那个...你还记得吗 别说了
Uh , that...You remember that thing ? Stop talking .
你有没有我们以前经常做的
Do you have that thing that we used to do a lot
现在我已经不怎么做了的东西
and now I'm not doing too much anymore ?
你知道我在说什么吗
Do you know what I'm talking about ?
- 最上面的抽屉 - 太好了 谢谢
- Top drawer - Great , thanks .
- 不是你想的那样 - 抱歉杰克琳
- It's not what you think - Excuse me , Jaclyn .
看路 谢谢
Walking , thankyou .
我应该继续吗
Should I keep going ?
我想也许现在是我们都休息一下的好时机
I think maybe now is a good time we all take a break
重新评估我们到底在做什么
and reassess exactly what it is we're doing here .
- 你的胃怎么样了 - 很好
-How's your stomach？ - It's fine .
- 你看起来很紧张 - 我没有
-You Seem Stressed - I'm not gtressed .
我只是觉得我有一个巨大的事情
ljust feel like I have this huge thing
一直困扰着我
that's hanging over me at all times .
能和你一起策划婚礼真是太好了
Well , it was nice almost planning a wedding with you .
好了 我来了 我能做什么
okay , hey , I'm here . What can I do ?
你需要我做什么吗
What do you need from me ?
只是他妈的座位卡
It's Just the fucking place cards .
你看过邮件了吗
D id you read the email ?
- 是的 看了 - 看了吗
- Yes．Yes - Yes ?
座位卡安排邮件 看了
The place card setting email . Yeah .
- 是吗 - 我很喜欢
- Yes？ -Loved it .
你最后一次和PJ出去是什么时候
When's the last time you hung out with PJ ?
我是说他是你真正的朋友对吧
I mean he's your actual friend , right ?
你为什么不和他谈谈
Why don't you talk to him about this ?
看 你很聪明
See , you're smart .
我想这就是我们要结婚的原因 对吧
I guess that's why we're getting married , right ?
是的
It is
你担心得太多了
You worry too much .
大多数人不会对他们的工作如此激动
Most people don't get so worked up about their job .
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be great .
你好 这里是
Hello , you've reached the law offices
凯 多诺万律师事务所的办公室
of Kay , Donovan , and Associates .
请留言
Please leave a message
我们会尽快回复你谢谢
and we'll get back to you as soon as we can , thanks .
我是劳拉
This is Laura .
请让杰瑞给我回电话
Please have Jerry call me back .
我在车里杀了雷蒙德
I shot Raymond in the car .
好的 我能来杯伏特加苏打水吗
Um , okay , can I just do a vodka soda please ?
- 两杯 - 谢谢
- Two please - Thank you .
- 谢谢 - 两杯 好吧
- Thank you - Uh , wow , two , okay .
好的 妈的 两杯 谢谢
Uh , yeah , shit , two please , thank you .
临阵退缩了吗
Cold feet ?
我们来这里干什么
What are we doing here ?
几周前
A couple of weeks ago ,
我收到一封信
I got a letter in the mail
邀请我在酒店房间里
inviting me to a no strings attached
进行无附加条件的性接触
Sexual encounter in a hotel room .
这是一张漂亮的邀请卡看起来很正式
It was a pretty card , looked official .
我不知道我太蠢了 我去了
I don't know , I was stupid , I went .
去你的 什么 伙计 这太疯狂了
oh , fuck you . What ? Dude , this is nuts .
我不得不戴上眼罩...
I had to wear a blindfold .
我应该留着的 但那个女人...
I should've kept it , but the woman...
我甚至不能告诉你
I can't even tell you .
你知道在多元宇宙系统中
You know that thing where something's different
宇宙内部的某些东西是不同的
inside of the universe in the multi-verse system
而这是唯一不同的地方
and this is the one thing that's different .
感觉就像这样 我不知道 很难解释
It felt like that . I don't know , it's hard to explain .
等等 等等
Whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa , whoa , wait .
这是怎么回事 等等
What's going on here？Hold on .
等等 这真的发生了 你真的这么做了
Wait , this is really happening , you really did this ?
在这种形势下
In this climate ?
伙计 你他妈的想自杀吗
Dude , are you fucking suicidal ?
我不知道
I don't know .
好吧 好吧 哇 我靠
okay , okay , wow , holy shit .
- 是啊 - 好吧
oh , yeah - Okay .
- 是啊 - 抱歉 好吧
- Yeah - Sorry , okay .
- 是啊 - 哇
- Yeah - Um , wow ,
我以为你是在生我签下雷蒙德的气
I thought this was you being mad at me for signing Raymond .
- 这是一个巨大的... - 你签下了雷蒙德了吗
- This is a huge．- You signed Raymond ?
你他妈的怎么签下雷蒙德的
How the fuck did you sign Raymond ?
好吧 等等 我们先不说那个
okay , well , hold on , let's...let's focus .
让我们把注意力集中在这件事上好吗
So , let's focus here , okay ?
好吧 我知道你是认真的
So , okay , so I know you're serious .
好吧 我们开始吧 首先 我很抱歉
okay , so let's do this . so first of all , I'm so sorry .
你来找我显然是没有其他选择
You clearly have no other options , you came to me .
没有回信地址 没有邮票
So there's no return address , no stamp ,
所以可能是亲自送来的 或者是快递送来的
So probably delivered personally or by a courier maybe .
你们大楼里有安全摄像头吗
Do you have security cameras at your building ?
你可能已经想过这些了
You probably already thought about all this .
- 是的 - 在过去几个月里
- Yeah - Has anyone reached out to you
是否有人在社交媒体上联系过你
on social media in the past couple months ?
这可能看起来很奇怪
It might seem strange .
也许有人想破坏婚礼
Maybe someone trying to sabotage the wedding
或者像是最后的狂欢之类的
or like a last hurrah kind of thing .
我想不起来...
I can't think of...
没有
NO
所以你看不到她 她戴着眼罩吗
So you couldn't see her ? Was she wearing a mask？
我想是的
I think so .
她在房间里的动作很敏捷
She was quick in the room .
她一开始绝对是戴着的
She definitely had it on at the beginning .
她一定也对家具了如指掌
She must've known her way around the furniture .
但后来我把它取下来了
But then I took it off .
我想她看到我的脸了 我想她认出我了
I think she saw my face . I think she'd recognized me .
你一个人在房间里吗
And you were alone in the room ?
哦 该死 现在我不知道了
oh , fuck . Yeah , now I don't know .
看 这就是我他妈一开始
See , that's the reason I wanted
想谈这件事的原因
to fucking talk about this in the first place .
你为什么不把眼罩摘下来呢
Why didn't you Just take the fucking mask off ?
我不想让她知道是我
I didn't want her to know it was me .
我不知道 推诿 自我保护...
I don't know , deniability , self-protec...
我不知道 我觉得我被吓坏了
I don't know , I think I was fucking terrified .
- 谢谢 - 给你
- oh , thank you - Here you go .
- 慢用 - 非常感谢
一Enioy - Thank you so much .
不知道那封信是从哪儿来的吗
No idea where that letter came from ?
我很抱歉告诉了你这些
I'm sorry I told you all of this .
不 伙计 完全没事
No，dude , totally fine .
现在我怀疑每个人
Now I'm suspicious of everyone .
也许是你老婆
Maybe it's your wife .
也许是我老婆
Maybe it's my wife .
伙计 这可能是任何人 也有可能是以前的客户
Dude , this could be anybody . This could be an ex-client .
不对 是CAA 一定是的
Nope , this is CAA . Yep .
你知道 我想过这个
You know , I was thinking about this .
我考虑过做这样的事情
I was thinking about doing something like this
作为一种生意
as a businesg .
但我不再能这样了
Can't do this shit anymore .
背着我的妻子吗
With my wife ?
她全家都是律师
Her whole family's lawyers .
她会把我的头砍下来
She would cut my fucking head off .
然后逍遥法外
She'd get away with it .
伙计 如果我有收到这种东西
Dude , if I got one of these fucking things ,
我会睡在收发室里
I would be sleeping in that mail room .
雷蒙德·李 享年58岁
对不起 请结帐好吗
Excuse me ! Can we get a check , please ?
我的人生他妈的糟透了
My life is fucking terrible .
你好 我想投诉这栋公寓
Hi , I'd like to file a complaint against the building .
哦 不 我很遗憾 发生什么事了
Oh , no , I'm sorry to hear that . What's going on ?
我的一个朋友被谋杀了 我被抢劫了
A friend of mine was murdered and I've been robbed .
也许是同一个人 我想在打911之前
Maybe by the same person . I thought I'd go to you
我应该先来找你 因为我是个他妈的成年人
before calling 911 'cause I'm a fucking adult .
天啊 发生什么事了
Oh , my God , what happened ?
我要看监控录像
I need to see security camera footage
2月22日的
from the 22nd of February ,
前门大厅死胡同
the front lobby , the cul-de-sac
以及任何能通往收发室的地方的录像
and anything that leads to the mail room .
有人给我留下了死亡威胁
Someone has been leaving me death threats .
而且 我是一名警官
And also , I'm a police officer .
天啊 你...好吧
Oh , God . You're...okay .
我们会尽力帮忙的
Uh , well look , we'1I do everything we can to help ,
但我觉得我们不能...
but I don't think we can show...
好吧 不行 我需要看监控录像
Okay , no , so I need to see security camera footage
我他妈的现在就要看
and I need to see it right fucking now .
嗨 我在和一个跟踪狂打交道
Hi , I'm dealing with a stalker
为了我未来的妻子 我尽量保持洽静
and I'm trying to stay calm for the sake of my future wife
她现在在楼上 吓得半死
who's upstairs right now scared half to death .
- 我很抱歉 - 是啊 你很抱歉
- I'm sorry to hear that - Yeah , you're sorry .
他很抱歉 我们都很抱歉 大家都很抱歉
He's sorry , we're all sorry , evervbody's sorry .
让我们看看监控录像 好吗
Let's see security camera footage , right ?
- 这是公司政策 - 好吧 不行
- It's corporate policy．- Okay , no .
好吧 我们再试一次
All right , let's try this again .
你好我叫乔丹·海因斯我是一个很棒的房客
Hi , my name is Jordan Hines . I'm an excellent fucking tenant .
我从来不来这里我的房租总是准时交
I never come down here . My rent is always on time .
我是那种你永远不用担心的人
I'm one of those guys you never have to worry about .
当人们开始把自己的公寓租出去时
或者浴缸一整个月没有热水的时
I didn't complain when people started Airbnb'ing out their apartments
我都没有抱怨
or when the hot tub was cold for a fucking month .
我不会离开 我不会不自在
I'm not going away . I'm not uncomfortable ,
我的客户喜欢和我在一起
my clients enioy spending time with me .
让我看监控录像
Let me see security camera footage
2月22日的
from the 22nd of February
我也不会花几千美元
and I won't spend thousands of dollars
让印度的外包工们
having an Indian click farm
在Yelp点评网上轰炸了你的公寓
bomb your fucking apartment complex on Yelp .
就在那扇门后面
It's right through that door .
我知道它的确切位置
I know exactly where it is .
现在 还有什么问题吗
Now , is there a problem here ?
哪里是寄送诉讼的最佳地点
Where's the best place to send a lawsuit ?
我最好把诉讼寄到哪里
Where'gthe best address for me to send a lawsuit to ?
这里 这里停下
There . There stop .
看到没 看到没
See ? See ?
别让那些怪人进来
Don't let fucking weird people into the building
那些没有钥匙卡的人 好吗
who don't have a key card , okay ?
这家伙到底是谁
Who the fuck is this guy ?
只有我一个人吗
Am I alone here ?
这家伙到底是谁
Who the fuck is this guy ?
这里不是汽车旅馆
This isn't a motel.
我可不是花钱住汽车旅馆的 好吗
I don't pay to live in a fucking motel , okay ?
这家伙到底是谁
Who the fuck is this guy ?
这玩意儿他妈没电了
ThiS is fucking dead .
现在你彻底没电了
Now you gotta die .
现在你他妈的彻底没电了
Now you fucking gotta die .
-一坨屎 - 嗨 抱歉
- Piece of shit - Hey , hi , sorry .
对不起 对不起 对不起 我没有暴力倾向
Sorry , I'm so sorry , I'm so sorry , I'm not violent .
我只是想和你谈谈 我有个问题要问你
I just want to talk to you . I got a question for you ,
我有个问题要问你 对不起 我有个问题要问你
I got a question for you . I'm so sorry . I got a question for you .
- 救命 - 他妈的闭嘴 好吗
-Help! - Shut the fuck up , okay ?
我有个问题 对不起 谁付钱给你
I got a question for you , I'm sorry . Who's paying you
- 把东西送到我的公寓的 - 去你的 别挡我的路
- to deliver shit to my building？ - Fuck you , get out of my way .
你在给我的大楼送东西
You're delivering shit to my building .
我有权知道 好吧 我明白你可能觉得
I have a right to know . okay , I get it , you probably have
是因为我的裸照什么的 这没什么大不了的
naked pictures of me , it's not that big of a deal .
它是怎么工作的 告诉我你是怎么工作的
How does it work ? Tell me how you work .
- 救命 - 他妈的闭嘴
- Help! - Shut the fuck up .
他妈的闭嘴 好吧 对不起
Shut the fuck up . okay , I'm sorry .
听着 如果你他妈想要现金的话 我不会随身带现金的
Look , I don't carry cash on me if that's what you fucking want .
好吧 我只想知道你为谁工作
okay , yeah , I Just need to know who you work for .
谁付钱让你给我的大楼送东西的
Who's paying you to deliver shit to my building ?
我不想听到 哦 我不知道我不在那里之类的话
I don't want to hear "Oh,I don't know, I wasn't there" .
- 我为一个应用软件工作 - 这里是好莱坞
- I work for an app - This is Hollywood .
这是个重要时刻 好吗
This is the big time , okay ?
他妈的别动
Don't fucking move .
他妈的别动 呆在那儿别动
Don't fucking move ! Stay right there .
别再给我的大楼送垃圾邮件了
Don't deliver Junk mail to my building anymore ,
好吗 混蛋
okay , asshole ?
我会调查的
I'm gonna look into this .
- 有什么事吗 - 嘿 我的好兄弟
- Can I help you？ - Hey , there's my guy .
我住在附近 我在街上发现了一些邮件
I'm a neighbor and I found some mail in the street .
有个混蛋已经打开了
Some asshole already opened it
但我想知道路易丝·拉弗蒂在家吗
but I'm wondering if Louise Rafferty's home ?
露易丝已经离开我们了
Louise is no longer with us .
真方便
That's convenient．
你说什么
Excuse me ?
听着 伙计 我是个私家侦探
Look , buddy . I'm a private investigator .
今天别跟我耍花招
Do not fuck with me today .
我需要露易丝回答一些问题
I need some questions answered by Louise
我想马上和她谈谈
and I'd like to talk to her immediately .
- 嗨 对不起 - 哦 她来了
- Hi,I'm sorry - oh ,there she is .
- 进去 - 有什么问题吗
- Go back inside - is there a problem ?
没什么
It's nothing .
这个人很困惑
This man is confused .
他弄丢了他的狗
He lost his dog
他在附近发传单
and he's handing out flyers in the neighborhood .
哦 是什么样的狗
Oh . What kind of dog is it ?
是一只可卡犬...它是一只斑点狗
It's a cocker span...It's a Dalmatian .
我很抱歉...
I'm so sorry for your...
我不知道这是个葬礼
I had no idea it was a funeral.
我得走了
I have to go
谢谢你抽出时间
Thank you for your time .
我们会注意你的狗的
We'll keep an eye out for your dog .
是的 谢谢我们已经派人去找了
Yeah , thank you . We got people looking .
她经常钻到汽车下面 所以...
She gets under cars and stuff so...
怎么了
What's up ?
- 操你没事吧 - 没事
-Oh , fuck , you all right？ - Yeah .
- 天啊 - 对不起
- Jesus - Yeah , sorry .
伏特加苏打 双份 谢谢
Vodka soda , double . Thanks .
好吧 这玩意儿太疯狂了
All right , so this shit is crazy .
- 那么信封...没事吧 - 没事
- So the envelopes...Are we good？ - Yeah , we're fine .
- 你确定吗 - 是的
- You Sure？ - Yes .
好吧 信封是原装的
Okay , all right , so the envelopes are stock .
它们是由位于伯班克的爱马仕邮政公司生产的
They're made from this company called Hermes Post in Burbank .
他们是一家在线公司他们生产很多这样的东西
They're this online company . They make a bunch of those
像是公司派对邀请函什么的
corporate party invites and shit .
这正是我们所担心的
Which is what we were worried about .
好莱坞的邮政信箱是匿名的
The P.0. box in Hollywood is anonymous .
它是通过网站设置的，所以这又是一个死胡同
It's set up through the website so that's another dead end .
- 好了 该死 - 等等 好了 停下
- All right , shit - Hold on , all right , stop .
好的 这是件很简单的事情
okay , that's the easy stuff .
嘿 我们要的那两杯能快点吗 谢谢
Hey , can you make that two , actually ? Thank you .
好吧 我要说了 等我说完
Okay , I'm gonna talk and I'm gonna finish ,
你想说什么就说什么
and then you can say whatever you're gonna say .
但是请让我说完
But please Just let me get through this
因为这很重要好吗
'cause it's important . okay ?
好吧
Okay .
好的
当社交媒体平台刚开始出现的时候
When social media platforms first began ,
仅仅基于人与人之间的联系
they were based solely on connecting people ,
但后来被扭曲了
but then they were bastardized
变成了赚钱的机器
and turned into these money-making machines
它们会收集你的数据 然后卖给广告商
that would harvest your data and sell it to advertisers .
比如说你在大学的时候点击过什么东西
So say you clicked on something back in college ,
所有那些点击所有那些点赞
all those clicks , all those likes
从那时起一直到现在的
from then all the way till now ,
都被这些公司保存起来了
that's all been saved by these companies .
然后在2013年
And then in 2013 ,
他们开始允许其他公司使用这些数据
they started allowing other companies to use that data
来锁定你作为消费者的
to target you as a consumer
所有具体兴趣和行为
for all your specific interests and behaviors .
你在推特上的每一个点赞都是公开的
Every like on Twitter you've ever had , that's all public .
你可以查看任何人的社交媒体账号
You can go on anyone's social media account
看到他们从一开始就喜欢的一切
and see everything they've liked from the beginning .
现在所有的数据都是可以被收集
Now , all of that data is scrapable .
这意味着有人想出了一个程序
同eaning someone could come up with a program
从你完整的在线数字足迹中
that would compile all of that data
汇编所有这些数据
from your complete online digital footprint
并利用它来更好地了解你 以及如何接近你
and use it to better understand you and how to get to you .
如果我在做这件事 我会把目标对准有钱人
And if I were doing this , I'd go after the wealthy .
比如说你在社交媒体上
So say you're on social media
你关注福布斯兰博基尼
and you follow Forbes and Lamborghini
还有游艇俱乐部和好莱坞经纪公司
and Yacht Clubs and Hollywood agencies , yeah .
最重要的是假设你还订婚了
And on top of that , let's say you're also engaged
而且在过去的三个月里
and that for the past three months ,
你也断断续续的
you've also been off and on
点赞半裸女性的照片
Iiking pictures of half naked women .
- 我操 - 让我说完
- Fuck me - Let me finish .
半裸女性
Half naked women .
那就意味着 第一
That would mean one
你可能赚了很多钱
you probably make a lot of money ,
第二 只需要稍微推一下
and two , with a little push ,
你就可能偏离现在所处的关系
you'd probably stray from your relationship .
这样那个人就可以把你和另一个一模一样的人配对
So that person could then pair you with someone identical ,
一个在你看来很完美的人
someone who would seem perfect to you .
- 还需要什么吗 - 没了 请你滚开
- Is there anything else？ - No , please fuck off .
谢谢你
Thank you .
对不起 伙计 我...对不起
I'm sorry , man , I...I'm sorry .
这将使你成为这项新服务的
Which would make you an incredible candidate
不可思议的候选人
for this new service .
我们又没有赚多少钱
We don't make a lot of money .
我们的行为就像我们假装出来的那样
We act like we do .
你租爱彼迎或者住酒店
You'd rent out Airbnbs or hotels ,
你知道的 一些令人向往的东西
you know , something aspirational ,
然后他们就抓取到你了
and then they'd have you .
这是最终的点击诱饵 渴望陷阱
It's the ultimate click bait , thirst trap .
就是...查查看
Uh , it's when , uh...Just look it up .
事实上 别查
Actually , don't...
别担心 没关系的
Don't worry about it , doesn't matter .
重点是...
The point is...
通奸率大幅下降
adultery's down drastically .
人们非常害怕越界
People are so terrified of stepping out of line at all
他们甚至都不谈论这个
they don't even talk about it .
因为必有后果
'Cause consequences won't go away anymore .
《红字》
Scarlet letter .
世纪美国的清教徒殖民社会里一宗年轻少妇在丈夫失踪的情况下跟当地牧师产生奸情
《红字》是的
Scarlet letter , yeah .
公众曾经是坏人
The Public used to be the bad guy .
还记得吗
Remember that ?
我的意思是 这对创业公司来说是个好主意
I mean it's a great idea for a startup .
匿名
Anonymous .
就只需要酒店房间...
Cost of a hotel room...
还有几张邮票的费用
and a couple stamps .
是你在这样对我吗
Are you doing this to me ?
不是
No
好吧 伙计 最重要的是
All right , dude , most importantly ,
一个女人在富兰克林大街被谋杀了
a woman was murdered off Franklin Ave .
2月21日那天
on February 21st ,
地点就离你公寓三个街区
three blocks from your apartment .
家庭纠纷 瑞典人 无前科
Domestic dispute , Swedish , no priors ,
看起来完全正常的人 我查了他们的资料
seemed totally normal people , I looked them up .
那家伙捅了她
The guy stabbed her
把她从阳台上扔下去
and threw her over a balcony .
警察在案件发生前就接到报警电话
Cops were responding to a call she made beforehand .
他们把那家伙带进来的时候
When they brought the guy in
他还对美国邮政服务大喊大叫呢
he was screaming about the US Postal Service .
她案件发生前就报警了吗
She called beforehand ?
这听起来像我的风格
This sounds like me .
我也这么想
I thought so too .
我们能结账了吗 伙计
Hey , can we close out , man ?
对不起 先生 我们可以结账了吗
Excuse me , sir . Can we close out , sir ?
现在不要...不理我啊
Just not...just gonna ignore me now .
我得向你道歉
I'm gonna have to apologize .
先生
sir ?
- 喂 - 丽萨 我是乔丹
- Hello？ - Lisa it's Jordan .
- 哪个乔丹 - 姓海因斯的 你好吗
- Jordan？- Hines , how are you ?
乔丹啊 我很好你呢
Hey , Jordan , I'm good , how are you ?
我很好 我只是想打个电话
I'm doing well . ljust wanted to call .
我想我们毕业后就没说过话了
I guess we haven't spoken since graduation .
你最近怎么样 最近在哪里安顿啊
How are you doing ? Where are you living these days ?
实际上我还在布伦特里
I'm still in Braintree , actually .
罗斯和我最后到了同一家医院工作
Ross and I ended up at the same hospital .
真幸运
Oh , well , that's lucky .
你最近去过洛杉矶吗
You ever make it out to Los Angeles ?
我没有
I don't .
有一个蹒跚学步的孩子 这很难
It's tough with a toddler .
哇 太疯狂了
Wow , that's crazy .
因为我好像在富兰克林街上看到你了
Because I thought I saw you on Franklin
几周前是你吗
a couple of weeks ago . Was it you ?
不 不 不是我
Uh , yeah , no , not me .
一定是和我面貌相似的人
It must've been my doppeiganger .
你喜欢洛杉矶吗
How are you liking LA ?
我爱洛杉矶
I love LA .
距离湖边大约一小时车程
About an hour from the lake ,
戒酒五年 工作十年
five years sober , working on my ten .
太好了
That's great .
太好了 恭喜你
That's so great to hear , congratulations .
我就知道你会熬出头的
I always knew you'd figure it out .
你确定不是你吗
You sure it wasn't you ?
我只是想...
I just thought...
几天前你加了我的领英
you'd added me on Linkedln a couple days earlier .
我几乎可以肯定是你
I was almost certain it was you .
哦 不是
Uh , no
你只是突然出现在了推荐关注的列表里
You popped up as a suggested follow ,
我想是因为同一个学校的缘故吧
because of school I guess .
我...我以为 你知道 我最近没见过你
I...I thought , you know , I haven't seen you .
我很确定
I was pretty sure .
我猜你甚至不会告诉我 如果有的话 是吗
I guess you wouldn't even tell me if it was , huh ?
我不知道你在问我什么
I'm not sure what you're asking me .
我很抱歉 这很不舒服
I'm so sorry . This is uncomfortable .
这听起来像是
This sounds like one of those phone calls you hear about
一个白痴晚了十年打电话给你
where some idiot calls you ten years late
然后让自己出丑了 对吧
and makes a fool of himself , isn't that right ?
不 不 我只是想确定你没事
No , no , I Just want to make sure you're okay .
我很好 一切都很好
I'm fine , everything's great with me .
我一定是又打扰你了
Uh , I must have disturbed you again
我很抱歉
and I'm so sorry about that .
这不是中年危机
Uh , this isn't a midlife crisis .
如果我有这种情况我会告诉你的
I'll let you know when I'm having one of those .
- 没关系 - 我没事
- No , it's fine - I'm fine .
一切都很好 我只是想问个清楚
Everything's fine . I Just wanted to check in
那边一定很晚了 对不起
It must be so late over there , I'm so sorry .
祝贺你拥有的一切
Congratulations with everything ,
谢谢你和我联系
thanks so much for the connect
我们都很兴奋
and , um , we're all excited .
那么晚安...
So , uh , good night and , um...
是的 晚安 是的 就这样
And yeah , goodnight , yeah , that's it .
恭喜你订婚了
All right , congrats on your engagement .
好的 谢谢 再见 好的 再见 保重
Yeah , great , thankyou , bye . All right , bye now , take care .
汪汪
Woof .
杰克琳 出现得正是时候
Hey , Jaclyn , perfect timing .
我想知道你明天是否能把我的所有电话
I'm wondering if you can send all my phone calls
都转移到我的手机上
to my cell tomorrow
因为我要去东边开会
'cause I've gotta boogie to the east side for some meetings .
别担心我会赔偿的
Don't worry about that . I'm gonna pay for it .
很抱歉
Sorry about that .
我会赔偿的
I'm gonna pay for it .
无线网断了
Ugh , wi-fi's down .
嗯哼
Mm-hmm .
是你把这条毯子放在这儿的吗
Did you throw this blanket on here ?
看起来不错
It looks nice .
这是蜜月旅行时买的
It's from the honeymoon .
啊
Ah
需要点什么吗
Can I get you anything ?
是的 过来
Yeah , come here .
过来坐
Come sit .
我告诉你
Man. I'll tell ya
我们该如何处理这些事情
What do we do with all this ?
你知道 这些天我花了很多时间在片场
You know , I spend so much time off set these days .
我们离开这吧
Let's just go .
我们回到罗马的别墅去
Let's go back to that villa in Rome .
我们可以让我妈妈出来走走
We can have my mom come out .
你恨罗马
You hated Rome .
不对 我只是讨厌那些宫殿
No , I hated the palaces .
你买一座宫殿是为了那些远离该死的人群
You buy a palace to get awav from the fucking crowds .
如今你甚至无法看到艺术品
Nowadays , you can't even see the artwork
因为每个人都在它面前
because everybody's waving
挥舞着那该死的照相机
a thousand fucking cameras in front of it .
你觉得怎么样
What do you think ?
我可以让本在Zillow房地产网站看看
I can get Ben to look on Zillow
看看我们能不能在罗马买个房子
to see if we can buy a place in Rome ?
你说呢
What do you think ?
听起来像是个梦
Sounds like a dream .
一个好梦 不是吗
A good dream ?
救命
Help .
好了 伙计们 接下来是有趣的部分
Okay , guys , now this is the fun part .
- 我们要用虾 - 你没事吧
- We're gonna take the shrimp..．- You all right ?
没事 这很令人兴奋 我很喜欢
Yeah , it's exciting , I love it .
热量会使它更容易被包裹起来
The heat's gonna make it easier to wrap .
但我们得确保我们不会烧伤自己
Let's make sure we don't burn ourselves .
- 你确定吗 - 是的 我只是有点热 亲爱的
- You sure？- Yeah , I'm Just hot , honey ,
我就在炉子旁边 还穿着这件愚蠢的衣服
I'm right next to the stove andI'm wearing this stupid fucking outfit .
- 感觉怎么样 卡罗琳 - 还行吧
- How are we doing over here , Caroline？- Fine I think .
好吧 我们忘了胡萝卜片
Okay , well we forgot the carrot slices
不过没关系 我们可以随时煮...
but that's okay , we can always boil...
不实际上我们不想把胡萝卜片和我们的放在一起
No，actually we don't want carrot slices with ours .
- 非常感谢 - 不 要做就要做对
- Thank you so much - Nope , let's do it right ,
至少第一次得这样好吗
at least the first time , okay ?
卡罗琳你去拿点胡萝卜吧
So Caroline , you want to grab those carrots ?
不 别帮忙 停下 我...我们不需要...
No，don't help , stop . I...We don't need any...
好吧 对不起 我只是有点热 我就在...
Okay , I'm sorry , I'm just hot , I'm right next to...
我能把这个拿下来吗 可以吗
Can I take this off ? is that all right ?
穿着这身衣服我觉得自己要窒息了
I feel like I'm suffocating in this fucking outfit .
伙计 只是...只是做饭 伙计 我们在做饭
Dude , Just...Just cook , dude , we're cooking .
- 是的 谢谢 PJ 我正在做饭 - 好的 酷不用担心
- Yeah , thanks , PJ , I am cooking - okay , cool , no worries .
你需要出去呼吸一下新鲜空气吗
Do you need to mavbe go outside and get some fresh air ?
不用 我不需要出去
No , I don't need to go outside .
我是来做饭的 让我们做饭吧 去他妈的 对吧
I came here to cook , let's cook . Fuck it , right ?
现在我意识到我提高了嗓门
And now I realize I've raised my voice .
现在我觉得我他妈的疯了
And now I feel like I'm losing my fucking mind
因为没人想承认这一点
'cause nobody's acknowledging it .
兄弟 嘿 嘿 我觉得出去呼吸点新鲜空气
Buddy , hey , hey , I think maybe it's a great idea
是个好主意
for you to just go outside and get some fresh air
另外再想想看
and just think about the fact that
我们不得不假装这是我们的主意 好让你的未婚妻
we had to pretend this was our idea so your fiance
可以和你共度他妈的美好时光
could spend some quality fucking time with you so ,
春卷 我们在做春卷
spring rolls , we're making spring rolls .
一旦它们被卷起来 我们就可以把它们叠在一起
once they're rolled , we can stack them beside each other
排成一排排的
into nice little rows .
如果它看起来很奇怪 也没有关系
It doesn't matter if it looks weird ,
味道应该会很不错
it'll taste good , probably .
- 对不起 - 我没事
- I'm sorry - I'm fine .
-不 不好意思 - 我没事
-No，I'm sorry - Uh-uh , I'm fine .
我不是故意的 我不知道自己怎么了
I didn't mean to do that . I don't know what's wrong with me .
我们停下 离开这里
Let's stop , let's get out of here .
我们走吧 我不想变成这样
Let's go away , I don't want to be like this .
我能看到自己在做什么我不想变成这样
I can see myself and I don't want to be like this .
我不知道我怎么了
I don't know what's wrong with me .
好吧 我懂了 我懂了
Okay , I get it , I get it .
假装做你自己
It must be absolutely exhausting
一定很筋疲力尽
pretending to be you .
嘿 我是乔丹·海因斯
Hey , you've reached JordanHines .
我将在山区不与人联系
I'm gonna be out of contact in the mountains
要为我们的婚礼做一些场地考察
doing some venue scouting for our wedding ,
但我同时也有空
but I'm also available .
好的 好的 再见 保重
okay , yeah , great , bye now , take care .
我现在一直都有这种恐惧
I have this fear all the time now
我周围有一大群人
that there's this crowd of people around me
对我评头论足
judging me
就等着我犯错...
just waiting for me to slip up...
这样他们就可以给我涂上焦油和羽毛...
So they can tar and feather me...
或者把我赶出公司
Or drive me out of town .
我想我到最后都会一直
And I think I end up thinking about these people
想着这些人...
so much...
我有时候会忘记自己真正的想法...
that I sometimes forget what I really think...
以及我对某些事的真实感受
how I really feel about something .
当你和别人友好相处的时候 我会看着你
I watch you when you're friendly with people
我不知道你是像
and I don't know if you've made friends
普通人那样在交朋友
the way that normal people make friends
还是你只是为了工作
or if you're just doing it for the job
我想你也分辨不出来
and I don't think you can tell the difference either .
好吧 这是什么
okay , what is this ?
这是关于乔丹的周末吗
Is this a fuck Jordan weekend ,
带我来山上就为了侮辱我吗
take me to the mountains and insult me ?
亲爱的 我不是在侮辱你
Honey , I'm not insulting you .
我是在描述你
I'm describing you .
- 你能不能别说了 - 什么
- Would you just stop？ - What ?
这样我就可以...你看着我
So I can...So you can look at me
- 当我在和你... - 我在看着你
- like look at me when I'm...  - I'm looking at you .
你在说什么 我看着你呢
What are you talking about ? I am looking at you .
你没有对我说实话
You're not being honest with me .
你甚至不能说实话
You can't even be honest about being fucking honest .
- 不是这样的 - 你要去哪
- That's not true - Where are you going ?
我哪儿也不去
I'm not going anywhere .
我以为这就是那条小路
I thought this was the trail .
是你把我逼下来的
You pushed me off the fucking trail .
我没有逼你
I'm not pushing you .
我们在他妈的树林里
We're in the middle of the fucking woods .
- 跟我说话 - 我在跟你说话
- Talk to me! - I'm talking to you .
- 但是对我说实话 - 我对你说实话
- But be honest with me - I am honest with you .
这不是你的假关系之一
This is not one of your "fake" relationships .
我是你的未婚妻 他妈的和我谈谈吧
am your fiance , fucking engage with me .
- 我爱你 - 我也爱你
- I love you - Yeah , I love you .
好吧
Okay
- 你来吗 - 当然
- Are you coming？ - Yeah , I'm coming .
不 亲爱的 我觉得他会做得很好
No , honey , I think he's gonna do a great job .
我只是想知道你是否还能找到
I'm just wondering if you could've picked
一个比他更老套的婚礼策划人
a bigger cliche of a wedding planner .
哦 你要嘲笑
oh , you're gonna make fun of someone
一个假装对工作充满热情的人吗
for faking enthusiasm for their job ?
嗯 我能要...我不知道 还是卡布奇诺吧
Um , can I do a...I don't know , cappuccino .
加蜂蜜 你们有蜂蜜吗
With honey . Do you have honey ?
这家伙想要一杯大杯美式咖啡
And this fella wants a large Americano
再加一杯
with an extra Shot .
一杯薰衣草拿铁 我想就这样了
A latte with lavender , I think it was .
你们有什么特别推荐吗
Do you have a special ?
哦 如果我买...
Oh , if I buy...
嗨
Hi .
你认识我吗
Do you know me ?
- 你说什么 - 抱歉 打扰了
I'm sorry？ - Sorry to interrupt .
你怎么认出我的 我又不出名
How did you recognize me ? I'm not famous .
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about .
- 你可以继续假装 - 好的
- You can keep going - Oh , okay .
- 嗨 我是汤姆 - 嗨 汤姆
- Hi , I'm Tom - Hi, Tom .
你怎么认出我的 我叫乔丹·海因斯
How do you know me ? My name is JordanHines .
你叫什么名字
What's your name ?
有什么问题吗
is there a problem ?
不再是问题了 汤姆 我他妈的很好
Not anymore , Tom , I'm fucking great .
我们该走吗
Should we leave ?
你们都可以走了
Y'all can go .
所以你知道我在说什么
So you do know what I'm talking about ?
嗨 你说你好 我也说你好
Hi , you say y'all . I say y'all too .
你从哪里来的
Where you from ?
嗨
Hi .
我想他把她误认成别人了
I think he's mistaking her for someone else .
没错 我以为你是我认识的女演员
That's right . I thought you were an actress I know .
你叫什么名字 这是我未婚妻卡罗琳
What's your name ? This is my fiance , Caroline .
你叫什么名字
What's your name ?
嗨
Hi .
抱歉 亲爱的
Uh , sorry．Honey ?
我需要你去车里等着
I think I need you to go wait in the car .
- 是工作 - 嗯哼
- It's work - Mm-hmm .
我们需要打电话给谁吗
Do we need to call somebody ?
不 你不用打电话给任何人
No , you don't have to call anybody
因为她现在就要大声说出她的名字
'cause she's gonna say her fucking name out loud right now
然后我就可以走出去了
and I'm gonna walk right out of here .
在这之前我是不会走的
I'm not leaving .
它是如何工作的
How does it work？
你知道吗
Do you even know ?
你是妓女吗
Are you a prostitute ?
操
Fuck !
当然她当然会离开
Of course! Because of course she leaves .
你好 我是卡罗琳·盖茨 请留言
Hey , this is Caroline Gates . Please leave a message .
亲爱的 听我解释
Hey , sweetie , let me explain .
她是一个作家 一个崭露头角的新人
She's a writer and an up and coming new voice ,
新鲜的声音 女性的声音
fresh new voices , female voices ,
多样性现在真的很流行
diversity is really in right now ,
我想和她签约参演我们的一部电视剧
and I wanted to sign her for one of our TV productions .
所以 当然它必须得是在今天
So, of course, it has to happen today of all days .
对不起 我很高兴今晚能向你进一步解释
I'm sorry , I'm excited to explain it to you further tonight ,
还有 嗯 是的 所以 晚安
and , um , yeah , so , yeah , goodnight .
啊
Ah !
啊 该死
Ah, fuck !
你想走向爸爸吗
You want to walk to Dada ?
是的 是的 等等 等等
Yeah , yeah , hold on , hold on .
- 快点 - 该死 等等
- Come on - Shit , hold on .
等一下 等一下 抱歉 嘿
one second , one second , sorry．Hey .
嘿 你有钱吗
Hey , you got money ?
什么 没有
What? No .
等等 你找到那个人了吗
Wait, did you find the guy ?
没有 我要做一件非常愚蠢的事
No，I'm about to do something very stupid .
我需要你今晚把我保释出来
I need you to bail me out of Jail tonight .
你他妈的在说什么 等等 伙计
What the fuck are you talking about ? Hold on , man .
告诉我你在哪儿 我跟你一起去
Just tell me where you are , I'1I go with you .
我现在不方便说话 如果我晚上6点前不给你打电话
I cannot talk right now . If I don't call you by 6 p.m.,
打911找出我在哪 我会还你钱的
call 911 , find out where I am and I'll pay you back．
- 嘿 你还好吗 - 别逞英雄
- Hey , how you doing？ - Don't be a fucking hero .
- 你会搞砸的 - 亲爱的 是谁
- You're gonna fuck this up - Sweetie , who is it ?
乔丹 等等 亲爱的 对不起
Jordan．Hold on honey , I'm so sorry .
可能没什么事 我下午6点给你打电话
It's probably nothing . I'll call you at 6 p.m.
好的 好的 再见 保重
Okay , all right , yeah , bye now , take care .
好吧 对不起 亲爱的 对不起
Okay, I'm sorry honey. okay I'm sorry .
嗨 亲爱的 我很抱歉
Hi honey , I'm so sorry .
爸爸的同事是个白痴 嗨
Daddy's coworker's an idiot , hi .
爸爸需要学会划清界限
Daddy needs to learn boundaries .
我知道 爸爸需要学会保持距离
I know , daddy needs to learn boundaries .
- 麦卡利斯特探员 - 请叫我布鲁斯
- Agent McAlister - Please , call me Bruce .
没问题 这是刘易斯 我是雷别卡
No problem . This is Lewis , I'm Rebecca ,
我们是迈克尔的助手 他还是迈克尔的儿子
we're MIChael's assistants. He's also Michael's gon .
我不知道我为什么这么说 谢谢你能来
I don't know why I said that . Thank you for coming .
- 带路吧 - 要喝点什么吗
- Lead the way - Can I get you something
- 喝点什么 咖啡吗 - 不 非常感谢
- to drink , a coffee？ - No , thank you do much .
我得了溃疡
I have an ulcer .
就这些吗
These are them ?
是的 这些就是我们的紫色信封
Yep , these are our purple envelopes .
这是我们较小的四边版本
This is our smaller four bar version .
我们是为了那些送花的订单做的
We get those ordered for flower deliveries .
这是我们较大的合法尺寸 适合11x14
This is our larger legal size . It fits 11x14 .
这是一个较大的
It's a bigger fabric paper .
这是我们的A9皇家紫色信封
And that is our A9 roval purple envelope ,
通常是在婚礼上用的
usually ordered for weddings .
它们很贵吗
And they're expensive ?
最贵的一种
Thev're up there .
它们的颜色很有趣
They're a funny color .
大多数新娘喜欢白色
Most brides prefer white .
有时候他们也很喜欢他们
Sometimes they take a liking to'em ,
但我们没卖出多少
but we haven't sold many .
除了最近 是吗
Except for recently ?
除了最近
Except for recently .
所以大约三个月前 我们接到了一个批量订单
So , about three months ago , we had a bulk order placed .
都是在网上订单的
These are all done online .
我们的打印机很大 它们是密封的
our printer's gigantic , they're sticker sealed .
什么都可以打
From soup to nuts , you can have an order done
你可以在一个小时40分钟内完成一个订单
in an hour and 40 minutes
印刷 书法 金箔 怎么样都可以
printing , calligraphy , gold leaf , anything .
直到它进入盒子之前
Until it hits the box
除非需要邮资或者快递来取
and needs postage or a courier picks it up ,
我的团队都不会去碰它
my team doesn't touch it .
订了多少
And how big was the order ?
314 .
314这个订单很大吗
314 , and that's large ?
在阿纳海姆 我们每天印刷6000份
We print6,000 a day in Anaheim .
314那是π 有什么意义
314 . That's pi . What's the significance ?
这家伙是个该死的数学狂
The guy's a fucking mathlete ?
对不起 我太沉迷于案件中了
Sorry , I get very close to my cases .
我知道我没有必要问
I know I don't have to ask but you guys don't have
但你们没有这家伙的地址 对吗
an address on this guy , right ?
他用信用卡付的钱 你肯定知道他们的名字 对吧
He paid with a credit card , you gotta have a name for them , right ?
是的 这是网上购买的
Yes , this was an online purchase .
这是一份以约翰尼·贝宝的名义订购的订单
It was an order under the name of Johnny PayPal .
约翰尼·贝宝 不 这不是个真名
Johnny Pay , no , that's not a real name .
没人会叫约翰尼·贝宝
Nobody's called Johnny PayPal .
对不起
I'm sorry .
好吧 他通过贝宝或Stripe支付
Okay , so he pays through PayPal or Stripe
或者其他在线支付平台
or some online Service .
也许他有一个有限责任公司或帐号
Maybe he has an LLC or an account number .
告诉我你们有相关信息
Tell me you guys have an EIN．
在我看来 这就像是在妨碍司法
That just looked like obstruction of justice to me .
把那该死的文件给他
Give him the fucking paperwork .
对不起 妈的 妈的
I'm so sorry , fuck , fuck .
紫色信封有限责任公司
Purple Envelope LLC .
314个信封 花了他多少钱
314 envelopes , what did that run him ?
全套946美元 包括内卡
$946 for the full package , including interior cards .
三千吧
Let's call it three grand .
他妈的做这些就只需花三千块吗
Motherfucker did this for three grand ?
我猜他还得付酒店的钱
I guess he had to pay for the hotels ,
除非他拥有这些酒店
unless he owns the hotels .
你是说这家伙杀了两个人
You're saying this guy killed two people ?
你觉得这能帮你们抓到凶手吗
You thinkthis is really gonna help you catch this guy ?
可以的 迈克尔 你做的是对的
I do , Michael . You're doing the right thing .
- 非常感谢 - 你身上有身份片吗
Thank you so much for this - Do you have a card on you ?
我们不带卡 刘易斯 警察局的才带卡
We don't carry cards , Lewis , police departments carry cards .
哇
Wow .
亲爱的
Honey!
卡罗琳
Caroline!
州务卿商业搜索
亚利克斯·帕蒂拉 加利福尼亚州州务卿
搜索条件 紫色信封有限公司
送达代收人：约翰尼·贝宝
地址：加利福尼亚州洛杉矶
格林布什大道4200号1B室
邮编90028
就是他了
There he is .
不好意思
Excuse me .
几周前这里发生过事故吗
Was there an accident here a few weeks ago ?
四号公寓 瑞典人
Apartment four , Swedish people ,
你知道我在说什么吗
you know I'm talking about ?
不 不 我不知道
No，no , I don't .
好吧
Okay .
你知道1B公寓在哪儿吗
You know where apartment 1B is ?
我觉得是个地下室
I think it's a basement .
知道 伙计 就在那条路的右边
Yes , man，just down that way to the right .
哦 该死
oh , shit!
妈的 停下 停下 住手 住手
oh , fuck! oh , stop , stop , stop .
操 操 操 停下 住手
Fuck , fuck , oh , fuck , fuck , stop . Stop!
你他妈的怎么进来的 妈的
How the fuck did you get in here ? Fuck!
妈的 停下 停下 好吧 好吧 操
Fuck , stop , stop . okay , okay , okay , fuck .
妈的...你他妈的是谁
Fuck...Who the fuck are you ?
你想要什么 你想要钱
What do you want ? You want money ?
我会给你钱的
I'll get you money .
操
Fuck .
是的 我知道你是谁 你就是那个混蛋
Yeah , I know who you are . You're that fucking guy .
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead .
这几天到处都是这样的事
It's been going around these days .
约翰尼·贝宝 你没有派任何人送信
Johnny PayPal , you didn't send somebody ,
之前那个人就是你吧
that's fucking you under there , huh ?
是的
Yeah .
真可惜
Shame .
好吧
Okay
Okay , yeah .
你就是那个没有回复第三封信的人
You're the guy who didn't respond to the third letter .
其他人都这么做了 混蛋
Evervbody else did , fucker .
你让我觉得它没有发挥作用
You made me think it didn't work .
这太棒了
This is great .
你要苏打水还是什么
You want a soda or something ?
你没收到第三封信吗
You didn't get the third letter ?
黄色的那个小家伙
Little yellow one ?
该死
Oh fuck .
你甚至都不知道 这样很合理
You don't even know . That makes more sense .
所以你现在在这里 为了什么 打死我吗
So now you're here , for what , to blow me ?
不 妈的
No . Fuck .
第一封信是介绍 第二封信是房间钥匙
First letter's the intro , second letter's the room key ,
第三封信是联系你 你们都得给我汇五千块钱
third one connects you . You both wire me five grand
然后我告诉你另一个人是谁
and I tell you who the other person is
你就是那个没有回信的人
and you're the guy who didn't write back .
哦...
Oooooooh...
对不起 我知道这个故事的结局
Sorry , I know how this one ends .
好吧
Okay , so , yeah ,
现在你想知道她是谁了
now you want to know who she is .
所以现在你只需要我帮你联系一个人
So now you just need me to connect you to somebody .
感觉怎么样
How does that feel?
不是很好 对吧
Not too good , right ?
我可以这么做
I could do that .
你介意吗
Do you mind ?
好吧
Okay .
发送中
Sending .
到处都是 他们正在发送中
All over , they're sending .
恭喜你 你耍了自己
Congratulations , you played yourself .
你什么都不是
You're nobody .
你不能把人们联系起来 我可以
You don't connect people , I do .
我不需要变得漂亮 我就是互联网
I don't need to be pretty , I'm the internet .
我帮了你一个忙
I did you a favor
你只是一块数据
You are Just a piece of data
我的系统是从索尼黑客那里抄袭过来的
that my system scraped from The Sony Hacks .
你甚至不是一个人
You're not even a person .
你是发生在我身上的一件事
You are an event that has happened to me .
我为你找到了你搜索历史上一直在寻找的灵魂伴侣
I found you your search history soul mate .
你应该对我三跪九叩
You should be kissing my asshole .
现在你又想要她了
And now you want her bad
而我永远不会告诉你
and I'll never tell you .
现在发出的信件数量是以前的一千倍
A thousand times as many letters going out right now ,
阿尔法级别
the alpha .
下个月将有10亿美元
That's one billion American
打入我的银行账户
coming to my bank account next month .
你是坏人 我赢了
You're the bad guy . I win .
滚出我的地下室 兄弟
Get out of my fucking basement , bro .
格伦 打911 我被打了
Glen , call 911 , I got fucked .
是的 没错
Yeah , yeah , yeah , yeah .
呃...公众
Ugh...the public .
他妈的 他妈的 他妈的
What the fuck! Fuck , fuck !
我操
Fuck me !
混蛋 该死的
Asshole , fucking shit ,
该死的废物 该死的混蛋
fucking loser , fucking asshole ,
狗娘养的 该死的
fucking son of a bitch , Goddamn it
去你的
Fuck you .
该死的
Goddamn it .
他妈的混蛋
Fucking piece of shit .
该死的混蛋
Fucking asshole .
他妈的混蛋
Fucking piece of shit .
他妈的废物 他妈的
Fucking loser . Fucking...
嘿
Hey .
她在这呢
There She is .
我之前在车里 然后我...
I was in the Car and then I...
所以 是的 我得和你谈谈
So , yes , I have to talk to you about something .
大约一个月前 我收到一封信
About a month ago , I got a letter
邀请我参加在酒店房间里的专属会议
inviting me to an exclusive meeting in a hotel room
当我到那里的时候 有一个裸体的...
and when I got there , there was a naked...
不 那是谎言 我知道她会在那里
Nope , that's a lie . I knew she was gonna be there .
操 好吧 说出来吧
Fuck , okay , let's do it .
该死的 说实话 好吗
Goddamn it , let's be honest , right ?
去你的 说实话
Fuck you , let's be honest .
好吧 诚实 诚实
Okay , honesty , honesty .
说实话
Just be honest .
说实话 这有多难
Just be honest , how hard is that ?
这是你爱的人
This is someone you love .
你会失去她的 说出实话
You're gonna lose her . Just be honest .
我又开始喝酒了
I'm drinking again .
我对尼古丁上瘾
I'm addicted to nicotine .
我在我的大楼外面只是个无名小卒
I'm a nobody outside of my building .
我花了一整天的时间试图给我楼层的人留下好印象
I spend all day trying to impress the people on my floor .
WGA之战只是个开始
The WGA fight's Just the beginning .
一旦其他工会介入 我们就完了
As soon as the other unions get involved , we're fucked .
他们不会让我们拿走所有的钱
They're never gonna let us take all the money .
为什么我们认为他们会让我们拿走所有的钱呢
Why did we think they're gonna let us take all the money ?
PJ跟我解释过了 我们正在成为旅行社
PJ explained it to me . We're becoming travel agents .
雷蒙德在派对上抓了我的老二
Raymond grabbed my dick at that party
没有人对此采取任何措施
and nobody did anything about it .
我们继续和那家伙一起工作
We kept working with the guy .
为什么我们还要和这些家伙工作
Why do we keep working with these guys ?
因为没有人知道发生了什么
'Cause nobodyknows what's going on
而且每个人都还是想成为哈维
And everybody still wants to be Harvey!
我们穿着得体
We dress nice .
我们想对下属大喊大叫
We want to shout at subordinates
和别人上床 然后逍遥法外
and fuck people and get away with it .
我等不及想要开始抓老二了
I can't wait to start grabbing dicks .
我不知道自己怎么了
I don't know what's happening to me .
诚实 我现在可以看到它了
Honesty , I can see it now .
你在湖边说的一切都是对的
Everything you said at the lake ,
我只是想变得酷一点 开心一点
I just want to be cool and happy
让人觉得我很有钱 很成功
and come across like I'm wealthy and successful
可我看起来真他妈的俗气
and I Just look fucking cheesy .
我不想再这样了
I don't want to do this anymore .
我恨死互联网了
I fucking hate the internet .
我只希望它还是21世纪初那样
I Just want it to be the early 2000s .
我想再次变得年轻
I want to be young again .
我还冒充了一个联邦官员...
I impersonated a federal officer...
好几次
couple times .
街那头的一个男人谋杀了他的妻子
A man down the street murdered his wife
而我是唯一知道这件事的人
and I'm the only person who knows about it .
她的名字叫路易丝·拉弗蒂
Her name was Louise Rafferty .
我的牙齿糟透了
My teeth are fucked .
我对我的助手很不尊重
I was disrespectful to my assistant .
她明天可能就会泄露我的电子邮件
She could leak my emails tomorrow .
我想我犯了邮件诈骗罪
I think I committed mail fraud .
我走下书架后面的楼梯
I went down the stairs behind the bookshelf ,
我在那遇到了歌剧中的魅影
I met the Phantom of the opera
然后我用锤子打了他
and I beat him with a fucking hammer .
是的 我没看
But no , I didn't look at
座位卡安排的电子邮件
the place card settings email ,
你也是这么想的
which is what you're thinking ,
我他妈看得出来
I can fucking tell ,
因为内心深处
because deep down
我是一个他妈根本不在乎的人
I'm somebody who just cannot give a shit .
特斯拉不是我的
I don't own the Tesla .
我一直在租用它
I've been leasing it this whole time .
我认为这个世界将会变成
I think the world's about to become
一个可怕的地方
a fucking horrifying place .
我想我只是看着它变成那样
I think I just watched it happen .
这是一个我永远无法控制的地方
It's a place that I would never have any control over .
你爱上我是因为我很强大
You fell in love with me 'cause I was powerful .
看看我现在变成了什么样
What am I gonna be now ?
是啊 来吧
Yeah . Do it .
妈的 我应该报警的
Fuck , I should have called the cops .
她很聪明
She was smart .
我就径直进入了这样一个状态
I walked right into this one .
我明白
I understand
如果我不是你想象中六天后要嫁的那个男人
if I'm not the man you thought you were marrying in six days
我很抱歉
and I'm sorry about that .
我只是不想再感到羞耻了
I Just don't want to be ashamed anymore .
我原谅你
I forgive you .
你好
Hello .
我是乔丹·海因斯
You've reached Jordan Hines .
因为所有的事情
Because of everything ,
我正在认真休假
I am taking a conscientious leave of absence .
请联系我办公室里的其他人
Please reach out to anybody else in my offices .
好的 再见 保重
okay , yeah , all right , bye now , take care .
你认为我们今天能走多远
How far do you think we can make it today ?
如果我们不停下来的话就会到边界
The border if we don't stop .
事情是这样的
So here's the deal.
所有这些事情 都不是什么新鲜事
All this stuff , it's nothing new .
虽然不同 但它并不新鲜
It's different but it's not new .
这可能是一次谈话
This could've been a conversation .
你知道 有人躲在黑暗中
You know , there are people out there in the dark
他们会竭尽所能破坏这一切
who will do everything they can to corrupt this ,
破坏我们所拥有的
what we have .
他们会对你微笑 他们会试图给你下套
They'll smile at you , they'll try to trip you up .
而我们的工作...
And our job...
从现在开始
from here on out
就是确保他们永远不会赢
is to make sure that they never win .
只要你准备好了
Whenever you're ready .
非常感谢
Oh , thank you so much .
又有八人死亡 纽约时报
Eight more dead，New York Times .
你能把那东西关掉吗
Will you turn that thing off ?
安贝 电话：613-9404
- 准备好了吗 - 好了
- You ready？ - Yep .
验收测试
已订婚
刚订婚（一年内）
预估达到
其中已订婚